Finding Aid for the Jack Hurst Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Little Theatre of Nashville Guild Collection
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0630
- Acuff to Benson
  - Roy Acuff, 2/5/88 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Roy Acuff -#1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Roy Acuff – Side 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Trace Adkins, 8/19/96 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Trace Adkins, 1/7/98 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Trace Adkins, 9/03/98 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Daniel Alexander, 11/7/89 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - All but inaudible bodyguard tapes (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gary Allan, 11/06/96 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Duane Allen, 1/14/91 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Rex Allen, Jr., 9/94 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - (A) John Anderson – 7/18/85 – (B) Forrester Sisters (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - John Anderson, 1/22/92 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - (A) Pete Anderson – 5/29/97 – (B) Jim Foglesong 5/30/97 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - (A) Sheila Andrews 1-9-80 – (B) Bobby Bare 1-11-80 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - (A) Eddy Arnold – 3/16/77 – (B) Jerry Clower 4-7-77 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - (A) Eddy Arnold – 3/16/77 – (B) Jerry Clower 4-7-77 (Copy 2) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Eddy Arnold, 5/30/89 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gerald Arthur, 10/15/87 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - (A) Chet Atkins 10/11/83 – (B) Christy Lane 10-21-83 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chet Atkins & Jerry Sullivan, 9/26/91 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chet Atkins, 8/16/94 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chet Atkins and Mark Knopfler (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Gene Autry, 3/16/83 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gene Autry, 2/16/98 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Hoyt Axton Part II (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - (A) Ross Bagwell & Cindy White– 7/31/92 – (B) Billy Ray Cyrus (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bailee and the Boys 7/9/87 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bailee and the Boys, 2/23/89 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bailee and the Boys, September of 1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - David Ball, 8/30/94 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - (A) Moe Bandy 6-10-87 – (B) K.T. Oslin (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - (A) Bobby Bare 4/14/83 – (B) Johnson Mountain Boys 4/15/83 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - (A) Bobby Bare 2/12/79 – (B) Dottie West 4/18/79 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bobby Bare, 1/11/1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mandy Barnett “Always Patsy Cline” 7/21/95 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - John Beland re: Rick Nelson (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Tom Becker, 11/3/87 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Benson – Jann Browne
  - Ed Benson, 5/1/90 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ed Benson, 10/94 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ray Benson, 10/25/88 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - (A) Ray Benson at Wilson Hall – (B) Dan Seals 7/?/90 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - John Berry, 9/22/94 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - (A) Vicki Bird – (B) Donnie Wilson (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alan Biyant, 9/15/98 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Clint Black, 4/19/89 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Clint Black, 6/12/92 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Clint Black, 1/23/97 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Clint Black – Half Way There (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - (A) Rick Blackburn – 9/23/87 – (B) Billy Joe Shaver (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - (A) Blackhawk –8/22/95 – (B) John Michael Montgomery 11/9/95 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Suzy Bogguss, 7/8/87 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Suzy Bogguss, 7/23/96 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Suzy Bogguss, Mid February (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Larry Boone, 1/12/88 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - James Bonamy, 8/20/96 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - (A) Jessica Boucher – 4/87 – (B) Kyle Young 4/?/87 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Jerry Bradley, 2/23/87 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - (A) Owen Bradley – 8/29/80 – (B) Willie Nelson 1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - (A) Billy Branch – 11/14/82 (B) Huey Meaux (& Freddy Fender?) 1/10/83 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - (A) Lane Brody – 4/15/84 – (B) Bob Atcher 5/25/84 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Paul Brandt, 12/9/96 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Garth Brooks, 3/23/89 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Garth Brooks, 7/12/90 (Side 2) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - (A) Garth Brooks – 9/16/91 – (B) Pam Lewis 9/18/91 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Garth Brooks, 11/29/94 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Garth Brooks, 11/03/95 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Garth Brooks (phone), 11/05/98 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Garth Brooks (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - (A) Garth Brooks – (B) Doug Sahm, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Brooks & Dunn, 10/1/91 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Brooks & Dunn, 5/6/93 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Junior Brown, 7/23/95 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Junior Brown, 11/19/98(?) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Marty Brown, 8/7/91 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Tony Brown, November 1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- BR 549 to Country Music Association
  - Jann Browne, 6/30/89 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - BR 549, 9/12/96 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - BR 549, 6/25/99 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ed Bruce, 10/13/82 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - * (A) Boudleaux Bryant – (B) Dottie Rambo (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Steve Buckingham (Vocal Tuning) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - John Bunzow, 3/20/95 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - (A) Jethro Burns – 6/14/84 – (B) Bob Atcher – (C) Allen Dawson & Bob Gibson 6/5/84 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Tracy Byrd, 4/6/95 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Campbell Bros @ Cracker Barrel near Opryland (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - (A) Paulette Carlson – (B) Ray Benson (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mary-Chapin Carpenter, 8/17/89 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mary-Chapin Carpenter, 10/26/90 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Carlene Carter, 5/29/90 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Deana Carter, 12/5/96 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - (A) Lionel Cartwright – 1/9/90 (B) Tony Brown 2/15/90 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Johnny Cash, 11/15/80 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Johnny Cash, 8/94 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - (A) Johnny Cash and June Carter – 4/1/84 – (B) Gina Lee King re: John Lair (Her father)5/31/84 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - June Carter Cash – May 27th (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - (A) Rosanne Cash – 3/27/90 – (B) Crystal Gayle – 3/27/90 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Rosanne Cash – early January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - * (A) Rosanne Cash – * (B) Michael Martin Murphrey Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Charlie Chase & Lorianne Crock, 3/11/92 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Mark Chestnut – Late 96 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - (A) Roy Clark 1/31/84 – (B) Nancy Jones 8/29/83 – (C) Chet Atkins 1/12/84 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Roy Clark 3/11/94 (at Sunset Grill) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Terri Clark (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Jane Cleveland, Teena Camp, Ken Mansfield & Steve West re: Nashville Pop (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - (A) Tammy Cline – 10/12/82 – (B) Brenda Lee re: ”The Winning Hand” 11/3/82 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Mark Collie, 4/3/90 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - (A) Bob Cooper (WSM manager) – (B) Roy Acuff (COPY of 33) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - (A) Bob Cooper (WSM manager) – (B) Roy Acuff (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Confederate Railroad, 2/13/92 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Dudley Cornwall, 12/16/87 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bob Corbin & Dave Hanner (Corbin/Hanner) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - C. Paul Corbin & Ralph Emery, June 1994 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Country Biographies, early 1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Country Music Association to Duffey
  - Country Music Association press conference 1/10/96 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Country Music In Europe (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Country Music Overseas (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Country Music Overseas – early 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Country Radio Interviews – May 1994 (Ed Benson, Tim DuBois, et al) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cox Family 7/7/92 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cox Family Part II (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Jim Crockett (Guitar Player Magazine) – early 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Rodney Crowell, 2/3/88 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Rodney Crowell, 2/20/92 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Billy Ray Cyrus, 3/29/92 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - (A)Billy Ray Cyrus – 11/07/94 – (B) Martina McBride (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Billy Ray Cyrus, 8/13/96 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Billy Ray Cyrus, 6/1/99 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lacy Dalton, 8/86 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lacy Dalton, 3/1/89 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Davis Daniel, 7/16/91 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - (A) Charlie Daniels – 8/24/79 – (B) Kitty Wells 8/24/79 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Charlie Daniels – November of 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Charlie Daniels, 7/31/98 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Gail Davies – Spring of 1995 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Chip Davis, 11/06/95 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - (A) Danny Davis – 1/24/80 – (B) Royce & Jeannie Kendall 3/15/80 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - (A) Jimmie Davis – 3/15/83 – (B) John Anderson – 3/3/83 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Paul Davis, 4/3/86 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - (A) Jesse Dayton – 3/19/97 – (B) Bill Engvall 3/20/97 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Billy Dean, 10/1/91 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Billy Dean, 5/7/96 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - (A) The Derailers (Brian Hofeldt & Tony Villanueva) – 9/10/97 – (B) Mark Collie 9/12/97 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - John H. DeWitt (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - (A) Lou Dewitt – 10/25/1985 – (B) Rick Rentz 12/6/85 – (C) Sonny West 12/9/85 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Diamond Rio 9/2/92 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - (A) Diamond Rio (Marty Roe) 7/3/98 – (B) Don Walser 7/9/98 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - (A) Joe Diffie – 10/22/1990 – (B) Hoyt Axton 11/6/90 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - (A) Joe Diffie – 8/14/91 – Don Reid (The Statlers) – 8/14/91 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Joe Diffie, 8/22/95 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Daryl Dodd, 11/14/96 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Charlie Douglas, 10/27/85 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Ducas to Gill
  - George Ducas, early 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - (A) John Duffey of Seldom Scene – 10/10/85 (B) Keith Whitley – (C) Joe Galante (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Holly Dunn, 6/28/89 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ronnie Dunn, 5/22/98 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hal Durham (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - (A) Don Epstein – 9/30/85 – (B) Martin Ragaway (CMA Show writer) 9/30/85 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Steve Earle, 8/1/95 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Ralph Emery, 11/8/91 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ty England, 5/23/95 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - (A) Don Everly – 6/11/86 – (B) ??? (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Skip Ewing (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Barbara Fairchild, 3/86 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - (A) Donna Fargo 1979? – (B) Connie Smith 6/8/79 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Jack Farris, 3/19/87 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Lester Flatt (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Rosie Flores and Mary Matthews (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Rosie Flores, 11/24/95 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Kathy and June Forester (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - (A) Fred Foster – 11/3/82 – (B) Jethro Burns 10/26/82 – (C) Charlie McClain (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Radney Foster, 4/14/93 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - (A) Foster and Lloyd – 10/6/87 – (B) Glen Campbell 10/6/87 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - George Fox, 4/9/90 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Jeff Foxworthy – August/ September of 1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cleve Francis, 12/21/91 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cleve Francis, 1/29/98 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Cleve Francis – early 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Elana Fremerman, 6/99 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - (A) Jamie Frizke – 10/10/83 – (B) Ricky Skaggs (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - (A) Garth Fundis – 7/31/91 – (B) Jerry & Tammy Sullivan (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Joe Galante @ RCA, 10/87 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - (A) Larry Gatlin – 5/18/84 – (B) Patsy Montana 5/24/84 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dave Gibson/Blue Miller, 2/12/93 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - (A) Don Gibson 12/20/76 – (B) Ernest Tubb 11/26/76 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Vince Gill, 10/5/91 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Vince Gill – early September 1992 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Vince Gill, 11/9/95 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Vince Gill, No Date (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Girls Next Door to Hobbs
  - Girls Next Door, 3/1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - William Golden of The Oakridge Boys, 9/9/1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Steve Goodman, 1/29/80 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - (A) Steve Goodman 4/15/85 – (B) Reba McEntire, 5/3/83 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - (A) Vern Gosdin 9/5/83 – (B) Terri Gibbs, 9/16/83 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Vern Gosdin, 12/29/87 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Vern Gosdin, 5/24/89 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - (A) Lee Greenwood – 2/10/84 – (B) Vince Gill – 3/29/84 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nanci Griffith, 4/25/89 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Jon Grimson – Americana Radio Format (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - (A) Merle Haggard –5-4-79 – (B) Eddy Arnold 5-4-79 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - (A) Merle Haggard – 9/26/82 – (B) Porter Wagoner 10/26/82 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Merle Haggard – early 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - (A) David Hall – 1/29/91 – (B) Moe Bandy 1/29/91 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - (A)Tom Hall – 8/21/82 – (B) Kris Kristofferson ?/25/198? (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - (A) Tom T. Hall 6/22/84 – (B) C. Paul Corbin – (C) Bill Scherezk (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - (A) Tom Hall – early September of 1985 – (B) Roy Acuff re: Patsy Cline – (C) Charlie Walker re: Patsy Cline (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - (A) Jim Halsey – 9/26/79 – (B) Ernest Tubb 9/28/79 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - (A) Jim Halsey – (B) Jeannie C. Riley (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Jim Halsey re: Billboard Song Contest, 7/24/90 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Wayne Hancock, 11/01/96 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Jeff Hanna (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - (A) Gus Hardin 7/26/83 – (B) Little Jimmy Dickens 8/17/83 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Emmylou Harris – 1/16/80 (Tape 1) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Emmylou Harris 1/16/80(Tape 2 – (B) Brain Ahern (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - (A) Emmylou Harris – 4/7/86 – (B) Marty Stuart 4/8/86 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - (A) Emmylou Harris Oct. 1980 – (B) Jim Glaser 10-11-80 – (C) Chet – (D) Janie Fricke 12-7-83 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Emmylou Harris, 6/15/87 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Emmylou Harris, 12/13/91 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - (A) Emmylou Harris 8/16/95 – (B) Steve Ripley (The Tractors) – 10/05/95 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - (A) Lib Hatcher – 1/8/87 – (B) Keith Whitley – 1/8/87 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Hee Haw (the new look) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Ty Herndon, 5/23/94 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Highway 101 – Nikki Nelson and Jack Daniels (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Benita Hill, 11/18/97 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - (A) Billy Hill – 8/3/89 – (B) Mike Snider 8/3/89 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Faith Hill, 11/93 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Faith Hill, 8/1/95 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - (A) Becky Hobbs – 5/17/88 – (B) Chet Atkins 5/26/88 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Holt to Kennedy
  - (A) Wendy Holcombe(B) Eddie Rabbitt – (C) Wendy Holcombe (again) 4/9/80 – (D) Tandy Rice 4/10/80 – (E) John Anderson 8/7/80 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - (A) David Holt – 6/30/88 – (B) Russell Smith 6/30/88 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Gerry House, 8/08/90 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - (A) James House – (B) Reyn Geyer – 11/17/88 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - (A) Kurt Howell of Southern Pacific – 5/8/90 – (B) Michelle Wright – (C) Brian Ferriman (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Marcus Hummon, 9/19/95 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Libby Hurley, 10/7/87 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Interviews on impact of radio price – early 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - (A) Mike Ireland (of Holler) late 1997 – (B) Marty Stuart late 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Alan Jackson, 3/19/90 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Alan Jackson, 3/27/91 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Alan Jackson 7/7/92 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - (A) Alan Jackson – 10/3/95 – (B) Trisha Yearwood 10/3/95 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Nisha Jackson, 5/12/87 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Jason and the Nashville Scorchers, 6/9/92 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - (A) Waylon Jennings, Jerry Reed 6/30/83 (B) Earl Thomas Conley 7/10/83 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - (A) Waylon Jennings – 11/20/83 – (B) Pinkard & Bowden 1/11/84 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - (A) Waylon Jennings 8/24/84 – (B) Gamble Rogers 8/30/84 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Waylon Jennings, 10/15/87 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - (A) Waylon Jennings –early 1992 – (B) Sammy Kershaw – early 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Waylon Jennings, 7/15/92 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Michael Johnson, 6/9/86 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - David Lynn Jones, 3/24/87 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - (A) George Jones – 9/5/83 (Country Explosion) – (B) Exile 2/9/83 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - George Jones – 4/4/89 (Jones Country) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - (A) George Jones and Nancy Jones – 4/1/84 – (B) Pee Wee King re: National Barn Dance 6/6/84 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - George Jones, 2/13/92 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - George Jones, 8/30/95 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Naomi Judd 11/17/93 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Naomi and Wynonna Judd, 3/24/95 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Naomi and Wynonna Judd – 3/24/95 (Side 3) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - The Judds, 9/16/86 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - The Judds, 1/87 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - The Judds, 8/10/88 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Wynonna Judd, 4/28/93 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Wynonna Judd, 5/12/97 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Lucy Kaplansky, 7/17/96 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Robert Earl Keen, 3/27/93 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Toby Keith, 1/6/93 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Keith to Loveless
  - Toby Keith, 10/4/94 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Toby Keith, 3/26/96 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky Headhunters, 12/28/89 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky Headhunters, 9/7/90 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Kentucky Headhunters (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ray Kennedy, 2/19/91 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sammy Kershaw, 8/3/94 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hal Ketchum – March-April 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hal Ketchum, 4/6/99 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - (A) Heather Kinsley – 10/8/98 – (B) Doug Johnson 10/13/98 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Kostas (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Kostas, 9/94 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Alison Krauss, 1/4/92 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Alison Krauss, 11/15/95 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Alison Krauss (Undated) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Celeste Krenz, 8/22/95 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Kris Kristofferson, 10/14/86 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Kris Kristofferson, 8/15/95 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - K.D. Lang, 1/14/88 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - (A) Nicolette Larson – 6/2/86 – (B) T. Graham Brown (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - (A) Lily May Ledford – 6/1/84 – (B) Lulu Belle 4/26/84 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Brenda Lee – Chicago- Fall of 1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - (A) Brenda Lee – 9/13/84 – (B) Don Potter 8/15/85 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Brenda Lee, 3/5/91 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Brenda Lee @ Opryland, 5/6/88 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Jerry Lee Lewis – 6/16/89 (Dennis Quaid press conference) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Jerry Lee Lewis, 6/16/89 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Jerry Lee Lewis, 6/16/89 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Pam Lewis, Nancy Russell & Kathy Gangwisch (Tabloid Tapes) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Terry Lickona, 1/15/90 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - J.E. Lighter- (May or so) 1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Dennis Linde, 10/3/93 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Little Texas, 3/5/92 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Lonesome Strangers, 3/30/89 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Lonestar @ BNA, 3/26/96 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - (A) Patty Loveless 10/86 – (B) Holly Dunn 10/86 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Loveless 1990 to Reba McEntire
  - (A) Patty Loveless – 5/10/90 – (B) Charlie Rich 5/10/90 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Patty Loveless, 3/30/93 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Patty Loveless – early 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Patty Loveless, 10/5/98 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Susie Luchsinger – around Xmas of 1987 in Oklahoma (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - (A) Loretta Lynn – 10/18/78 – (B) Boudleaux & Felice Bryant 10/25/78 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - (A) Loretta Lynn – 6/9/79 – (B) Mike Considine & San Fernando Valley Music Band 7/19/79 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Loretta Lynn, 11/86 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Loretta Lynn & Mooney Lynn, 12/13/94 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - The Maines Bros Band, 3/7/86 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Raul Malo, 7/23/98 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - (A) Barbara Mandrell – 11/1/78 – (B) Lulu Roman, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Barbara Mandrell, 3/9/79 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - (A) Barbara Mandrell – 11/29/79 – (B) Tom T. Hall 12/2/79 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - (A) Barbara Mandrell – 12/11/86 – (B) Greg Cahill 11/4/86 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Judy Massa, 12/15/87 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - (A) Wayne Massey & Charley McClain 7/25/85 – (B) Mac Vickery 8/5/85 – (C) Forrester Sisters 8/6/85 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - (A) Kathy Mattea – 6/24/84 – (B) Razzy Baily – 6/24/84 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - (A) Kathy Mattea – 8/9/88 – (B) George Strait 9/28/88 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - (A) Kathy Mattea – 9/20/89 – (B) The McCarter Sisters 7/31/89 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Kathy Mattea, 11/16/92 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Kathy Mattea, 12/10/93 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Kathy Mattea (Undated) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Mavericks, 6/8/92 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - The Mavericks – late 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Larry McBride, 3/15/84 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Martina McBride, 6/12/92 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Martina McBride, 10/13/94 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - (A) Lila McCann – 8/14/97 – (B) Willie Nelson 8/14/97 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - (A) Charly McClain – 2/2/83 – (B) Tammy Wynette 5/3/83 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Neal McCoy, 7/12/94 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Mindy McCready, 6/10/96 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - (A) Mel McDaniel – (B) Mel Tillis – (C) Rosanne Cash (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Bob McDill, 3/89 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Richie McDonald, 3/12/98 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Ronnie McDowell, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - John McEuen, 11/91 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - John McEuen, 8/26/94 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - (A) Reba McEntire (Undated) – (B) Bob Kirsch (Box 9, Folder 39)
- McEntire to O’Connell
  - (A) Reba McEntire – 8/87 – (B) Johnny Rodriguez 12/9/87 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Reba McEntire, 8/21/90 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Kirk McGee (of McGee Bros) – Approximately 30 min (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - (A) Graham McHugh – early 1994 – (B) Richard Landis (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kate Mckenzie (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Murray Mclauchlan, 6/9/89 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - * Don Mclean, 3/23/87 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - * (A) Jo Dee Messina – 10/04/96 – *(B) Megon McDonough – 11/15/96 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - * (A) Al C. Mifflin III – 1/6/83 - * (B) Gary Haber 1/10/83 - * (C) Huey Meaux 1/10/83 - * (D) Mickey Bryant of Gelfand (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - * Mark Miller of Sawyer Brown (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - * (A) Roger Miller – 7/8/83 / * (B) Earl Thomas Conley (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - * (A) Ronnie Milsap – Fall of 1986 * (B) Billy Joe Royal (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - * Ronnie Milsap, 2/23/89 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - # Brenda Lee Montgomery – Chicago, in the fall of 1979 (MISSING) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - * John Michael Montgomery – early 1993 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - *(A) Lorrie Morgan – 11/30/88 at Jack McFaddin’s office * (B) Interview with Bettye Shelton, wife of Ricky Van Shelton about Beefalo (Not Jack interviewing – unknown woman) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - * (A) Lorrie Morgan – 6/2/89 in her bus at Opry House (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - * (A) Lorrie Morgan – 3/12/91 * (B) 4 miscellaneous phone calls 1991 (Reba’s office after crash, Johnny Cash’s office and 2 others.) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - * Lorrie Morgan, 7/2/96 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - * Lorrie Morgan – No Date (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - (A) Gary Morris 1/6/86 (B) Charlie Daniels 1/8/86 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - * (A) Gary Morris – November 12th @ WB * (B) Ethel and The Shameless Hussies (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - * Michael Murphey – 9/13/90 on phone from Taos, N.M. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - * Michael Murphey – 11/18/93 at Warner Bros (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - David Lee Murphy – Spring of 1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - David Lee Murphy, 1/24/96 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - (A) Anne Murray – 2/27/84 – (B) Doyle Lawson of Quicksilver 3/5/84 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Anne Murray, 11/16/88 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Nashville Bluegrass Band, 12/12/91 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Bobbie Nelson, 8/22/80 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Susie Nelson, 8/7/87 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Tracy Nelson, 4/16/95 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Willie Nelson – early 1991 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - (A) Willie Nelson @ Chicago Fest – (B) Kathy Gangwisch (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Newgrass Revival, 8/7/84 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Newgrass Revival (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Juice Newton (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Maura O’Connell, 1/17/90 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- O’Connor to Rankin
  - * Mark O’Connor, 1/2/86 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - * Mark O’Connor, 11/6/97 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - (A) Mark O’Connor – Late 1997 – (B) Patty Loveless 12/?/97 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Jamie O’Hara – early 1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - O’Kanes (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - O’Kanes (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - (A) K.T. Oslin – 1/19/88 – (B) Sylvia (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - K.T. Oslin, 8/16/88 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - K.T. Oslin, 5/6/93 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - K.T. Oslin (Cont.) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Marie Osmond (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Merill Osmond, 4/14/87 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Buck Owens, 9/9/88 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - (A) Paul Overstreet – 3/87 – (B) Bonnie Gallie (Benita Hill) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Paul Overstreet, 2/19/91 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Prairie Oyster (Joan Besen, Russell deCarle, Keith Glass) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Lee Roy Parnell, 3/27/92 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lee Roy Parnell, 11/16/93 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Lee Roy Parnell, 11/20/95 (Box 11, Folder 19)